----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

 [Home](https://ipgmail.com/)  Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

The iPGMail app as a Commercial app. This application is intended for use as is.

This page is used to inform users about the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use the iPGMail app.

If you choose to use iPGMail, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that collected is used for providing and improving the app. Your information will not be shared with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use**

iPGMail collects no personal information and stores no information about the users or their data outside of the app and the device itself.  iPGMail does not share any information with any 3rd parties.

**Log Data**

In the event of an app crash, crash logs may be generated and stored on the device.  Crash logs may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app at the time of the crash, the time and date of your use of the app, and other statistics, but no personally identifiable information is stored in a crash dump or log file.  The crash log files are not transmitted outside of the device without the users consent and when they are transmitted, are only used for debugging purposes by the original author of the app, no 3rd parties are involved.

**Cookies**

This app does not use “cookies”.

**Links to Other Sites**

If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, you are strongly advised to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. iPGMail has no control over and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

**Children’s Privacy**

The app does not collect personal information on anyone, children or otherwise.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy maybe updated from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about the Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us using the support form at [https://ipgmail.com/support](https://ipgmail.com/support)

### Latest Tweets

Twitter feed is not available at the moment.

2024 © Copyright [iPGMail](https://ipgmail.com/ "OpenPGP Email security for iPhone and iPad")

Translate »
